Live forever. Hunt forever.
The Last Witch Hunter is a action, adventure,
fantasy film directed by Breck Eisner.
The modern world holds many secrets, but by far the most astounding is that witches still live among us; vicious supernatural
creatures intent on unleashing the Black Death upon the world and putting an end to the human race once and for all.
Armies of witch hunters have battled this unnatural enemy for centuries, including Kaulder, a valiant warrior
who many years ago slayed the all-powerful Witch Queen, decimating her followers in the process.
In the moments right before her death, the Queen cursed Kaulder with
immortality, forever separating him from his beloved wife and daughter.
Today, Kaulder is the last living hunter who has spent his immortal life tracking
down rogue witches, all the while yearning for his long-lost family.
Kaulder, played by Vin Diesel.
Dolan 37th, played by Elijah Wood.
Chloe, played by Rose Leslie.
Belial, played by Ólafur Darri Ólafsson.
The Witch Queen, played by Julie Engelbrecht.
Dolan 36th, played by Michael Caine.
The Last Witch Hunter is a 2015 American fantasy action film directed by Breck
Eisner and written by Cory Goodman, Matt Sazama and Burk Sharpless.
The film stars Vin Diesel as an immortal witch-hunter who must
stop a plague from ravaging the entire world.
The Last With Hunter premiered at the AMC Loews Lincoln Square in New York City on October 13, 2015, and was released in the United States on
October 23, by Summit Entertainment, being the last film distributed by the company before it was absorbed into Lionsgate.
The film received generally negative reviews from
critics, but grossed $146.9 million worldwide.
A sequel is in development.
The film explores themes of witch, new york city,
magic, superstition, black magic.